A Guide to the Papers of Emmanuel Episcopal Church, 1871-1983
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Emmanuel Episcopal Church, 1871-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10731
This collection consists of 16 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited on 1987 October 27.
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains parish registers, 1885-1983; vestry books, 1909-1977; Woman's Auxiliary minutes, 1871-1972; and financial statements, 1976-1977. With these are parish and church service registers of Holy Cross Mission, 1912-1942, a mission church of the Rev. F.W. Neve, Batesville, Va.
Contents List
- Financial Statements, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Parish Register, Holy Cross Mission 1918-1934 (Box 1)
- Parish Register, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1912-1935 (Box 1)
- Parish Register, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1935-1983 (Box 1)
- Register of Church Services, Holy Cross Mission 1912-1942 (Box 1)
- Vestry Books, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1909-1961, 4 volumes (Box 2)
- Vestry Books, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1961-1977, 2 volumes (Box 3)
- Woman's Auxiliary Minutes 1871-1913 (Box 3)
- Woman's Auxiliary Minutes 1915-1923, Oversize volume on shelf (Box 4)
- Woman's Auxiliary Minutes 1954-1972 (Box 4)
- Woman's Working Society Records, Emmanuel Episcopal Church 1871-1872 (Box 4)